University Senate; Records ua200
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislation, 1966-2006; 3; 3.5 cubic ft.
  - 6970-37: Establishment of the Governance Commission - Approved - March 25, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-38: Campus Center Information Desk - Approved - March 25, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-39: "Open" period for Meetings - Tabled - March 25, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-40: Special Committee on Faculty Evaluation and Term Renewal, Tenure, and Promotion Criteria - Approved - March 25, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-41: Council on University Evaluation and Improvement - Approved - March 25, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-42: New Statement of the Undergraduate Degree Pattern - Approved - April 20, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-43: Amendment to the "New Statement" by Inclusion of CURE - Approved - April 20, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-44: CURE Proposal - Approved - April 20, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-45: Doctoral Program in Philosophy - Approved - June 1, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-46: Master's Degree in Italian - Approved - June 1, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-47: Doctoral Program in Sociology - Approved - June 1, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-48: Master's and Doctoral Degrees in History of Science - Approved - June 1, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-49: M.B.A. Program - Approved - June 1, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-50: All-University United Fund Board - Approved - June 1, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-51: PPC Report on Salary Inequities and Teaching Loads - Recommitted - June 1, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-52: PPC Report on Discrimination in Retirement Plans - Approved - June 1, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-53: PPC Report on Guidelines for the Administration of the Trustees Policies - Recommitted - June 1, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - 6970-54: Research Policy of SUNYA - Tabled - June 1, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 10)
  - Summary of Legislation, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 11)
  - 7071-01: Powers of the University Senate - Approved - September 21, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-02: Right of Faculty Member to Appear Before Council on Promotions and Continuing Appointment - Tabled - September 21, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-03: Election of Committee on Nominations and Elections - Approved - September 21, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-04: Chairman of the University Senate - Approved - September 21, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-05: Quorum of Senate - Approved - September 21, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-06: Religious Holidays - Approved - September 21, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-07: Committee on student and Faculty Roles During Demonstrations and Confrontations - Defeated - October 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-08: Appearance of Faculty Members Before Groups Considering Their Promotion or Continuing Appointment and Notice of Departmental Action - Approved - October 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-09: Time in Rank for Promotion to Associate Professor and Professor - Approved - October 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-10: Off-Campus Greek Housing - Approved - October 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-11: Change in Student Affairs Council Membership - Approved - October 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-12: To Revise the Inter-Institutional Cross-Registration to Include Graduate Courses in Albany Law School - Approved - November 23, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-13: To Change Graduate Student Membership on the Graduate Academic Council - Approved - November 23, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-14: Notification of Departmental Recommendation Concerning Continuing Appointment - Approved - November 23, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-15: Waiver of Mandatory Consideration for Promotion - Approved - November 23, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-16: Suspension of Current Traffic Violation Disciplinary Action Procedures (Students) - Withdrawn - November 23, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-17: Parking Policy for the University - Approved - November 23, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-18: Extension of Current Senate Structure - Approved - December 7, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-19: Outstanding Teacher Award - Approved - December 7, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-20: Correction of Inequities in Faculty Salaries and Fringe Benefits - Approved - December 7, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-21: Multiple Major - Referred to Committee -, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - Resubmitted as "Double Major" - Approved - January 25, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-22: Approval of Ph.D. in German - Approved - January 25, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-23: Temporary Commission on Area College Cooperation - Approved - January 25, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-24: Outstanding Teacher Award Guidelines - Approved - March 22, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-25: Establishment of a Faculty Lounge - Withdrawn - February 15, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-26: Ph.D. in Library Science - Approved - February 15, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-27: Ph.D. in Anthropology - Approved - February 15, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-28: Area College Cooperation - Approved - March 22, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-29: Stop Signs - Withdrawn - March 22, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-30: Ph.D. in Social Welfare - Approved - April 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-31: D.A. in Economics - Approved - April 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-32: D.A. in English - Approved - April 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-33: D.A. in Physics - Approved - April 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-34: Judaic Study Year in Israel Program - Approved - April 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-35: Interim Plan for Graduate Student Representation - Defeated - April 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-36: Change in Name of the School of Library Science - Approved - May 3, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-37: Guidelines Concerning Promotion in Rank and Continuing Appointment - Approved - May 3, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-38: Environmental Studies Program - Approved - May 3, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-39: Second Field - An Interpretation Approved - May 3, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-40: B.S. Major in Social Welfare - Approved - May 3, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-41: Student Evaluations - Withdrawn - Referred to CUE & I, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-42: M. A. in Afro-American Studies - Approved - May 14, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-43: Ph.D. in Geology - Approved - May 14, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-44: B.A. Major in Music, General Program - Approved - May 13, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - 7071-45: B.S. Major in Business Education - Approved - May 13, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 12)
  - Summary of Legislation, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 13)
  - 197172-01: Priorities - September 13, 1971 - Referred to CEP - October 4, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-02: Membership on Grievance and Complaint Committee - September 13, 1971 - Defeated, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-03: Council and Committee Attendance - September 13, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-04: Membership on Council on Educational Policy - October 4. 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-05: Reprimand to Undergraduate Academic Council - October 4, 1971 - Withdrawn for 5-C, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-05-C: Undergraduate Grading - October 4, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-06: Membership on the Undergraduate Academic Council - October 4. 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-07: Membership on the Student Affairs Council - October 4, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-08: Group Automobile Liability Insurance - November 8, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-09: Academic Calendar - November 8, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-10: Membership in SPA - November 8, 1971 - No Action - December 13, 1971 - Withdrawn, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-11: Academic Calendar for 1972-73 - December 13, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-12: "Three Year Baccalaureate" - December 13, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-13: Money for SUNY Senators - December 13, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-14: Term Appointment Renewal - December 13, 1971 - Returned to Comm. - January 31, 1972 (Revised) - Returned to Comm. - February 28, 1972 (Revised) - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-15: College Level Examination Program - December 13, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-16: Physical Education Proposal - December 13, 1971 - Defeated, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-17: Change in Wording of Student Guidelines - December 13, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-18: Use of Volunteers in Library - December 13, 1971 - Tabled, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-19: Semester Hours - February 28, 1972 - Defeated, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-20: Decision-Making With Regard to Educational Policy - February 28, 1972 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-21: Tuition Policy - February 28, 1972 - Defeated, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-22: Determination of Prior Service Credits - March 27, 1972 - Withdrawn, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-23: Consideration for Continuing Appointment - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - May 19 1972 - Referred to EPC - Withdrawn, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-24: Senate Councils - March 27, l972 - Postponed - April 17, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-25: Council on Educational Policy - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - April 17, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-26: Undergraduate Academic Council - March 279 1972 - Postponed - April 24, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-27: Graduate Academic Council - March 279 1972 - Postponed - April 24, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-28: Student Affairs Council - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - April 24, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-29: Council on Research - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - April 24, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-30: Academic Services Council - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - May 11 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-31: University Community Council - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - May It 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-32: Council on Academic Freedom and Ethics - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - May 1, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-33: Council on Faculty Promotions and Continuing Appointments - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - May 13, 1972 - Referred to EPC, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-34: Council on University Evaluation and Improvement - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - May 11 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-35: Physical Education Requirement - March 27, 1972 - Referred to Undergraduate Acadmic Council - May 1., 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-36: Undergraduate Grading - May 19 1972 - Postponed, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-37: D. A, in Spanish - May, 8, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-38: Guidelines Concerning Promotions and Continuing Appointments - May 8, 1972 - Referred to EPC, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-39: Change in Trustees' Policies Concerning Term Appointments - May 9, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-40: Ad Hoc Committee on Teacher Evaluation - May 9, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-41: Change in Membership of Council on Educational Policy - May 9, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-42: Affirmative Action - May 9, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-43: Inclusion of Past Chairman of the Senate on the Senate - May 9 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - 197172-44: Interdisciplinary Major - September 5, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 14)
  - Proposed Bills and Resolutions, 1972 January-1972 December (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - Summary of Legislation, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 16)
  - 7273-01: Guidelines for Academic Calendars - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-02: Due Dates for Students' Bills - Referred to Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-03: Opinion Poll - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-04: Council on Promotions and Continuing Appointments - Defeated, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-05: Academic Calendar - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-06: Executive Committee - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-07: Amendment to Bill 7172-24 - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-08: Emeritus Status - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-09: Dormitory Inspection Policy - Referred to Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-10: Undergraduate Grading - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-11: Undergraduate Grading - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-12: Undergraduate Grading - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-13: Undergraduate Grading - Defeated, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-14: Undergraduate Grading - Defeated, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-15: Academic Rank Emeritus - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-16: Undergraduate Grading - Correction - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-17: B.A. with a Major in Greco-Roman Classical Civilization - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-18: Graduation Requirements - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-19: Alumni House - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-20: Privileges of the Rank Emeritus - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-21: Tuition Waiver Ceiling - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - 7273-22: Dean's List and Graduate with Honors - Section 1 Renumbered as 7374-09 - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - Proposed Bills and Resolutions, 1973 January-1974 December (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 18)
  - Summary of Legislation, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - 7374-01: Rules of Order - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-02: Academic Calendar for 1975-1976 Academic Year - Referred to Committee - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-03: Composition of Council on Promotions & Continuing Appointments - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-04: Composition of Council on Promotions & Continuing Appointments - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-05: Indian Quadrangle Dining Area - Referred to FSA, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-06: Outstanding Teacher Award - Referred to Committee - Withdrawn, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-07: Campus Firearms Policy - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-08: Examination of Student Medical Records - Referred to SAC, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-09: Dean's List - Criteria - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-10: Amendment to 1973-1974 Academic Calendar - Defeated (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-11: Permanent Representation of Students on University Senate - Withdrawn, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-12: Amendment to Guidelines for Preparing the University Calendar - Withdrawn in favor of 7374-15, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-13: Reconsideration of Tenure Decisions - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-14: Reconsideration for Continuing Appointment - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-15: Amendment to Guidelines for Preparing the Academic Calendar - Referred to Committee - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-16: Reconsideration After the Mandatory Year - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-17: Reconsideration of Continuing Appointment Decisions Made in 1972-1973 - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-18: Consideration for Continuing Appointment - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-19: Alumni House & Environmental Protection - Referred to UCC, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-20: University Car Pool Program - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-21: Revisions in Campus Bus Schedule - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-22: Regulation of Pets on Campus - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-23: Resolution on Tuition - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-24: Resolution on Parking - Withdrawn, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-25: Policy for Carrying Firearms on Campus - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-26: Amendment to the Rules of the Senate - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-27: Jurisdiction of Schools & Colleges in Establishing Academic Policies - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-28: Pre-Registration and Registration Procedures - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-29: Submitting Grades to Registrar - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-30: Amendment to Senate Implementation of the By-Laws - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-31: Date for "W" Grade - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-32: Reversal of Prior Recommendation - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-33: Amendment to the Charge of the CPCA - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-34: Resolution on Operational Guidelines - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-35: Student Participation in Promotion & Continuing Appointment Recommendations - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-36: Evaluation of Teaching - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-37: Student-Faculty Committee on Teaching - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-38: Performance Expectations - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-39: Personnel Committee - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-40: External Letters - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-41: Confidentiality of Personnel Proceedings - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-42: University Fountains - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-43: Bachelor of Arts Major in Judaic Studies - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - 7374-44: Bachelor of Arts Major in Puerto Rican Studies - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - Honors Policy, 1973; 1980 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - Summary of Legislation, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - 7475-01: Proposed Revisions in Guidelines for Promotion and Continuing Appointment - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - 7475-02: Transfer Credit for Balanced "D" - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - 7475-03: Part-Time Full-Status Appointments Within the Tenure System for Teaching Faculty - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - 7475-04: Resolution on Parking - Tabled, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - 7475-05: Statement of Belief Regarding the 1974-1976 Contract and Self-Governance at SUNYA - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - 7475-06: 1976-1977 Academic Calendar - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - 7475-07: Teaching Awards - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - 7475-08: Final Examination Policy - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - 7475-09: Resolution Regarding Outstanding Teacher Award - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - 7475-10: Conduct and Responsibility of Instructional Staff - Referred back to Council, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - Proposed Bills and Resolutions, 1975 January-1978 May (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - Summary of Legislation, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 24)
  - 7576-01: Amendment to the Composition of the Council on Promotions and Continuing Appointments - Approved - September 22, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - 7576-02: Revision in the Charge of the Council on Academic Freedom and Ethics - Returned to Council - Approved - November 3, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - 7576-03: CAFE Complaint Procedures - Approved - December 8, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - 7576-04: "Z" Grade - Returned to Council - February 9, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - 7576-05: Amendment to CAFE Complaint Procedures - Approved - February 9, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 25)
  - 7576-06: Patent Waiver Policy of SUNY Research Foundation - Approved - March 8, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (3-Legislation), Folder 25)